

Oleksandr Varynskyi

Junior Front-end Developer

Contacts

08.12.1994
oleksandrvarynskyi@gmail.com
+48-604-701-983
Lodz / Poland
github.com/varynskyi
linkedin.com/in/oleksandr-varynskyi

Personal skills:

Highly organized
Strong interpersonal Skills
Ability to solve complex problems
Collaborative
Discipline & Dependability
Verbal and written communication
Critical & analytical thinking
Detail oriented
Teamwork
Industriousness

Technical skills:

HTML5/CSS3/SASS GIT JavaScript React REST API Parcel Node.js

Languages

English B1 Polish B2 Russian C2 Ukrainian C2

Hobbies

Reading Traveling

Profile

Responsible and hard-working tech mind, highly passionate about programming. Focused on continuous self-development and improvement of my programming skills. Highly organized with exceptional commitment to task completion and quality assurance when working with computer software programs, motivated to deliver company objectives to projects and results to customers. I am capable of working with a variety of technology and software solutions, as well as managing databases. After achieving some of my own developments, I am ready to take up my first professional experience at the "Front-end" position. I am certain that my set of skills, including teamwork, workflow management, combined with my dedication to create beautiful web resources, will set me for success in my future role.

Own developments

- Web Studio [HTML5, CSS3, JS, SASS, BEM];
- HellEN [HTML5, CSS3, JS, SASS, BEM, Parcel]. Team project, role: developer;
- <u>Filmoteka</u> [HTML5, CSS3, JS, SASS, BEM, Parcel, Axios, Handlebars]. Team project, role: developer;
- Phonebook [HTML5, CSS3, JS, Axios, React.js, React router, React hooks, Redux];
- <u>Smart-finance</u> [HTML5, CSS3, JS, Axios, React.js, React router, React hooks, Redux]. Team project, role: developer.

Education

2011 - 2016

National Aerospace University named after N.E.Zhukovsky "Kharkov Aviation Institute"

"Specialist of Automation and Computer- Integrated Technologies" 05.2020 –05.2020

Online courses from the "Akademia kodu"

"Programmer specialty: Java basics"

01.2021 - 01.2022

Online training at the "GoIT" school, on the "FullStack Developer" direction

Job experience

05.2020 - present (Poland)

- Chef position in a restaurant sushi.

03.2018 - 05.2020 (Poland)

- Su chef position in a restaurant serving polish cuisine.